Murtaza Kankroliwala

I have 4+ years of professional expertise in full stack web and app development. I am a Keen learner and love to work on any Technical Stuff and ready to learn new things on Professional as well as personal aspect. Searching for opportunities to get experience and learn new tech stacks.

EXPERIENCE

LogisticsNow Pvt Ltd, Mumbai—Senior Software Developer

Oct 2020 - PRESENT

- 1. Full Stack Developer skilled in product, architecture, and design, ensuring seamless system integration and performance.
- Developing new live features on B2B Web and Mobile App bridging Transporters and Manufacturers, enhancing Supply Chain Logistics.
- Expertise in React and Python, leveraged Microsoft Azure tools (CosmosDB, Function Apps, SignalR, etc.) for robust application development.
- 4. Craft UI designs, user flows, Architecture with precision using Balasamiq, Figma, and draw.io.
- 5. Did Recruitment for Candidates for development roles.

Upcloud Technology, Remote—Team Lead, Full Stack Developer Intern

March 2020 - Oct 2020

- Development of Doctor's App using Flutter and Dart for a cutting-edge and efficient tech solution.
- 2. Designed a patient-centric web app for profile creation, appointment booking, and feedback/review system integration.
- 3. Served as a Tech Leader, guiding a team of 4-5 individuals to successful project outcomes.

LogisticsNow Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai— Associate Software Engineer Intern

December 2019 - March 2020

- 1. Built a ReactJS-powered Map webapp, showcasing proficiency in creating compact and functional location-based solutions.
- 2. Tested web applications, provided feedback, and contributed to bug resolution, ensuring enhanced performance and user experience.
- Participated as a developer in 24 hrs continous hackathon for building a basic app for test.

EDUCATION

KJ Somaiya College of Engineering, Mumbai —

B.Tech in Computer Engineering Jul 2017 - Oct 2020

M.M. Babasaheb Gawde Institute of Technology, Mumbai—Diploma in Computer Technology

Jul 2014 - Jun 2017

Nutan English High School, Mumbai—

SSC

Jul 2014 - Jun 2017

Dombivali, Thane-421201

Mob. No.: +91 98195 42253 Email: mkankroli3@gmail.com

Website

https://mkankroliportfolio.netlify.app/

LinkedIn Profile:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/murtaza-ka nkroliwala-938514168

SKILLS

React JS, Python, Azure, Flutter,
Full Stack Development,
App Development, Javascript,
Redux, MongoDB, Form
Recognizer,
Firebase, Google Cloud, Azure
Cloud, Architecture, Microservices

PROJECTS

B. Tech Project:

Fire Extinguishing Support System for fire station where user can report the fire station using app or using IoT if Alarms the nearest Fire Station for help.

Diploma Project:

TiffinVilla: Android Application to get user the home made food.

Inventory Management:

Short App Development for Rockford's where the drivers add their stock details and maintains transfer.

INTERESTS

Full Stack Development, AI/ML, Solutions Architect, Problem Solving, Debugging.

CERTIFICATIONS

Technical Leader in CSI – Diploma college Activities Kyrion tech – Ethical Hacking Workshop – IIT MumbaI